(This program contains indirect advertisements.)
(Taean)
(Embracing the blue waters of the West Sea)
(A place where vast tidal flats stretch out)
(Sun-kissed salt fields...)
(and bountiful farmlands stretch across the land.)
(Where there's an abundance of local produce)
(Taean in South Chungcheong Province where nature's gifts are everywhere)
(Today, a special festival is about to begin here.)
(Who is the first to arrive?)
One.
Two, three, four.
(Cho Jung Seok?)
Five, six, seven, eight.
(In a world of his own)
(Turning)
(Ta-da)
(The dance initiation is complete.)
(Cho Jung Seok arrives as a special guest in Taean.)
Okay.
(Jung Seok arrives 1 step ahead of the 4 siblings.)
How do you know Jung Ah?
- Well, I...
- What brings you here?
First,
we were in a movie called "Hit-and-Run Squad."
When I was in "Hospital Playlist,"
Sun Young made a special appearance.
I don't have her number or anything,
but somehow, I've had a strong sense...
of familiarity with her.
As for You Seok,
I'll be meeting him for the first time today.
He says that he wants to be like you.
You're his role model.
Really?
He's a big fan of yours.
Is that so?
I'm very grateful.
(How will You Seok react when he sees Jung Seok, his role model?)
Is that right?
- Shall we rehearse it?
- Sure, let's do it.
How about...
(Rehearsal?)
While staying outside?
They will be sitting here.
(Did Jung Seok prepare a special event before coming to Taean?)
(At that time, the four siblings...)
- Hello.
(Sun Young and You Seok are hand in hand.)
- Sun Young.
- Yes?
If we think about our work later, these aren't really mudflats.
- What? The tide will go out soon.
- The tide is still in.
(One person watching the scene unfold)
They're holding each other's hand.
(Watching them secretly while hiding)
They look so sweet together.
(Completely unaware of what's about to happen)
- Hello.
(Entering without suspecting anything)
My goodness.
It's beautiful. The view is amazing.
(A spot with a perfect view of the sea)
I seriously missed you so much.
You Seok is very happy to be back.
- I've been waiting for this.
- He says two nights are too short.
Right after filming here, he wants to go to the next location...
and continue filming.
We should film for two whole weeks...
until we get tired of seeing each other.
You Seok loves being on this show.
- What about you?
- I like it too.
I love being on the show too.
I want to spend 230 days with you all.
(While the two siblings are in love with Fresh off the Sea)
(Laughing)
(Jung Ah and Yoon Seo come running with huge smiles.)
(Completely happy)
We should hurry to see them.
- Isn't this place beautiful?
- My gosh.
It's really beautiful.
They're also holding hands.
Everyone here is so affectionate.
The older members are so warm...
and full of love.
Something smells delicious.
Aren't they workers over there?
- With them...
- Aren't they waiting for us?
(Are they waiting to head out to sea with the four siblings?)
We aren't getting abducted again, are we?
- You think so?
- I'm worried.
- Hello.
Did you see those people waiting for us?
- Where?
- Over there.
These aren't mudflats.
- Where are they?
- They're way over there.
I saw about ten people waiting for us.
- It must be a big boat.
- About ten people are waiting.
- That's worrisome.
- I know.
They're waiting for us, aren't they?
- I don't know.
- No?
- They always say they don't know.
- It's hard to believe them.
Steamed clams, kimchi crab stew, cold raw fish soup,
- and sea cucumber are recommended.
- Kimchi crab stew?
- "Crab?" - Is it a stew made with crab?
- Or clams?
- It must be a dish made with crab.
(Gasping)
It looks like shabu-shabu.
(It's a hearty feast.)
(To a refreshing, deeply flavorful broth,)
(a whole octopus dives right in.)
(A clear and refreshing octopus soup)
(Jaw-dropping)
Is it a crab?
- There are clams.
- Abalone.
It looks so good.
- There are abalone and shrimp.
- Incredible.
- It looks amazing.
- And squid.
(Clams underneath abalone, shrimp, and squid)
(Steamed clams, a generous harmony of seafood and clams)
(Manila clam soup packed with clams from Taean)
- That's a lot.
- It's cold raw fish soup.
I love cold raw fish soup. The portion is generous.
I've never seen it this beautifully presented before.
- I love it. It's so beautiful.
- It looks very delicious.
We're having such a healthy breakfast.
(Exclaiming)
- My gosh.
- Goodness.
- I love noodles.
- Gosh.
- The noodles.
- Goodness.
(A bowl of noodles mixed into refreshing cold raw fish soup)
I love this dish.
(Slurping it down neatly)
(One tangy, refreshing bite to wake up the appetite)
Shall I try it?
(Sun Young starts with steamed scallop.)
(Her eyes light up.)
Is it good?
- Gosh, the scallop...
- We're a little...
Abalone.
(Tearing off the plump, chewy abalone)
Is it good?
(Taking a huge bite)
It's good.
(I'll try some octopus soup too.)
(Scooping up a generous serving)
Thank you.
(Passing it to the youngest)
(It looks delicious.)
(Yoon Seo slurps up the broth.)
It's good.
(You Seok digs into the clam meat.)
It's a razor shell.
- A razor shell?
- Yes.
(You Seok digs into the clam meat.)
(Packed with the taste of the sea, how is the Manila clam soup?)
(Going straight for the chewy Manila clam)
(This is the taste.)
(Chuckling)
What's the matter?
- We'll probably catch one of these.
- Right.
- Which one will it be?
- Let's be relaxed when we eat.
(The creatures they might be catching today)
What's in season right now?
Clams and...
(It's a mystery.)
There's only one squid, so it can't be that.
(There's only one squid, so it can't be that.)
(Her guess is surprisingly well founded.)
If it's squid, there should be a lot of squid.
I don't care. Whatever it is, I'm going.
- We can handle it anyway.
- Right.
Of course.
After everything we went through last time...
(They're completely absorbed in guessing their work.)
(Meanwhile, Jung Seok makes his move.)
As a secret guest, I'm nervous.
I hope the hosts will be happy to see me.
(Sneaking off before anyone notices)
(Finally, he's right around the corner.)
(Warming up for one last time)
- We must be catching octopus.
- Octopus?
Octopus.
(The speculation about today's catch continues.)
As you know, we're in Taean now.
- Right.
- Today, you're heading...
- Yes.
to a rock festival...
- being held in Taean.
- What?
Gosh, that's awesome.
A rock festival?
(Bouncing her feet with excitement)
Why?
- Do you mean rock music?
- Why all of a sudden?
(Rock music in Taean?)
Why all of a sudden? This is awesome.
- A rock festival?
- We're going to a festival?
- Can we watch the concerts?
- But it seems quiet here.
You're lying.
- How are they lying?
- You'll let us watch the concerts?
We'll give you a hint.
My gosh. What is it?
Please give them a hint.
By "rock,"
- A rock?
- they must mean an actual rock.
(Suddenly, a red carpet appears.)
What's this? It's a red carpet.
(A mysterious red carpet spreads out.)
What's going on?
I hear music.
What is it?
Do we have a guest today?
- Seriously?
- We must have a guest today.
- We have a guest on the first day?
- Really?
Is it a rocker?
- This is amazing. What is it?
- Please come in.
(The song sounds familiar.)
Is Lee Jae Hoon coming?
Isn't it Cho Jung Seok?
I think it's Cho Jung Seok. Isn't it him?
- I think so. Jung Seok...
- I'm his huge fan.
Jung Seok?
(Could it be Cho Jung Seok, my role model?)
(Full of anticipation)
Really?
Is Cho Jung Seok coming?
(Really? Cho Jung Seok?)
(No way...)
There's only thing I hope for
(A guest artist at the rock festival, Cho Jung Seok)
(Screaming)
(Hopping with excitement)
(How about You Seok whose role model is Jung Seok?)
This is awesome!
Seriously?
(Blurred)
(He's so surprised that he forgot to swallow.)
My goodness.
- Jung Seok.
- Hello.
- I can't believe this.
(Are we dreaming?)
- Gosh.
- Nice to meet you.
(He also says hello to You Seok.)
This is awesome.
(Swept up in the warm welcome,)
(he finally gets to sing a little something.)
So it never loses its light
(The guest artist rolls up the red carpet himself.)
I'll stop here.
This is insane.
(Cho Jung Seok's surprise entrance is a huge success.)
- It's nice to meet you all.
- This is wonderful.
- Gosh.
- It's lovely to see you.
- It must be a rock festival...
- This is insane.
because of "Seok" in his name.
Last night, we couldn't stop talking...
- about who the guest would be.
- Seriously.
- I didn't imagine this at all.
- I'm so happy.
- I've been wanting to see you.
- I know, Yoon Seo.
This is amazing.
- I can't believe you're here.
- It's Cho Jung Seok.
Believe it or not, I'm here.
(They met once on Jung Seok's online channel.)
(Thank you for coming.)
This is unbelievable.
(Welcome)
This is so much fun.
- Seriously.
- We have a guest on our first day.
Thank you for welcoming me.
I'm so happy to see you, Jung Seok.
My plan was to sing while walking towards here.
I was going to sing here and say hello,
- but my plan went out the window.
- We ran towards you.
We got too excited.
(She was just so happy to see him.)
- We were so happy to see you.
- Thank you so much.
(Thank you for an enthusiastic welcome.)
I never imagined seeing Jung Seok in Taean.
- Please speak casually with me.
- What?
- Seriously, speak casually with me.
- Okay, Jung Seok.
I'm so excited. He's one of my favorite actors.
I've always felt a personal connection with you.
I'm your huge fan.
- I really like you too.
- Thank you.
- I also like you so much.
- I like you a lot.
- I like you even more.
- You're my favorite.
- No, I like you more.
- I like you more.
No, I like you even more.
(What's going on here?)
(You Seok just smiles without saying a word.)
(This is awesome!)
(Seriously?)
(His overwhelming admiration leaves him briefly speechless.)
(Just looking at him is enough.)
- Someone who looks like you...
- Why are you just smiling?
Me? Gosh.
I don't know what to say.
- Just looking at Jung Seok...
- I can't think straight.
I can't even think straight.
- Jung Seok...
- He's just so happy...
just to look at you.
- I feel like...
- With his role model...
- My heart is fluttering so much.
- Of course. I'd feel the same.
You Seok, please relax. I'll be casual with you too.
- Please do.
- Yes.
He's my number one...
- You love him very much.
- Whenever...
I'm not just saying this.
Whenever I'm being interviewed...
(A heartfelt confession from a true fan)
I always say that you're my role model.
I feel very grateful.
You'll be sleeping next to your role model tonight.
- You must be so excited.
- I won't be able to sleep tonight.
- I won't be able to sleep.
- My goodness.
- I envy you.
- I won't be able to sleep.
I feel nervous too.
Seriously.
(You Seok is blushing.)
- You must feel very shy.
- Yes, I do.
- What's the matter with him?
- What do we do?
I would never feel like this for any other guest.
(He's happy like he has the whole world.)
All right, hold my hand.
What is it about me that you like so much?
Things like this.
- His ears turned red.
- I know. He's on cloud nine.
- Gosh, thank you.
- My goodness.
(Jung Seok is touched by You Seok's genuine confession.)
- That must be nice.
- I don't know how to act.
Right.
I'm really curious.
Both Jung Seok and Gummy are incredible singers. Do they...
even go to karaoke together?
We used to go to karaoke a lot when we were dating.
- I see.
- Did you sing together?
The two of us.
You should've invited me.
I would've loved to listen to you sing.
- We can stay in the next room.
- Exactly.
- I want to hear them sing.
- Just listening to them...
We have a microphone at home with speakers.
- That's very good.
- We use that to sing together.
We really enjoy that.
It must be nice to sing with Gummy.
Right.
Watching them made me dream about getting married.
(Seeing Jung Seok and Gummy makes her want to get married.)
I only saw...
- the beautiful side of it.
- Right.
Married life isn't always like that.
- You've only seen that side.
- It's just one side.
(Laughing)
Jung Seok must feel hot.
No, I'm fine.
It's because I'm in the spotlight.
(Fanning him with their hands)
- I'm kidding.
- Oh, no.
Actually, it's nice and cool.
- It's because I'm eating hot food.
- Right.
(Peeling a shrimp quietly)
(Sending it straight to Jung Seok's plate)
- Counterfeit money...
- I see.
And so...
- What?
- I peeled one for you.
I was about to peel you one.
My goodness.
What are they doing?
- I saw You Seok peeling one, - Really?
so I wanted to peel 1 for him. Then I found 1 on my plate.
He's so thoughtful.
Thank you.
(Love is blossoming at the table.)
You Seok, say something.
I can't get any words out. What do I do?
(Jung Seok also peels a shrimp carefully.)
- You have to eat this part.
- Okay.
It's the best part of the shrimp.
(Enjoying the precious shrimp peeled by his senior)
I feel so good today.
I will work hard.
Let's work hard and earn a lot of money.
We should make him something delicious.
I'll also work hard.
(The four siblings promise to work hard.)
Anyway, you're here...
as a guest singer for today's rock festival.
(That's so funny.)
I only sang one verse.
(Laughing)
- One verse...
- It's time to go...
to the rock festival.
- Really?
- Seriously?
Weren't you just saying that because Jung Seok was coming?
- Is there a real rock festival...
- Really?
in Taean?
I didn't bring any outfit.
We need to dress up for a rock festival.
I thought that you meant the guest.
We must be catching crabs off the rocks.
- Right.
- Off the rocks.
- We're doing something on rocks.
- That's what "rock" meant.
They meant those rocks.
We wouldn't go to a real rock festival, would we?
(What exactly is this mysterious rock festival?)
- Shall we get going now?
- Let's go.
- Jung Seok.
- Yes?
- Let's go.
- Yes, let's get going.
(Just looking at him makes her smile.)
What exciting adventures...
(What exciting adventures await them?)
It's definitely a rock festival.
- Stop lying.
- If it's "rock,"
there will be crabs.
- We must be catching crabs.
- Crabs live between rocks.
- Crabs are also in season.
- We're definitely catching crabs.
I'll drive.
- Really?
- Yes.
You Seok, get in the front.
My goodness.
(You Seok claims the seat next to Jung Seok.)
Can you play that? I want to hear it again.
(Jung Seok recently released a new song.)
You don't have to play it.
But I want to hear it.
(Yoon Seo's first song pick of the day)
("You Changed My World" by Jung Seok)
I'm actually riding in the car Jung Seok is driving.
(Giggling)
- I'll take good care of you.
- Jung Seok is driving us.
(Riding in a car driven by their ultimate favorite)
- I'll learn this song quickly.
- Right.
(Listening to their favorite artist's song on the way)
(Naturally grabbing the handheld microphone)
(It's only you)
(Humming along with all her heart)
(My one and only love in this world)
(Frowning)
(I love you)
Yoon Seo already memorized the lyrics.
(She can't resist humming along even while getting ready.)
What's the title of the song?
"You Changed My World."
Yoon Seo, you really memorized it.
(Exclaiming proudly)
- "You Changed..." - "You Changed..."
- "My World." - "My World."
(They finished studying Jung Seok's new song.)
(Meanwhile, the fan quietly sitting in the front seat)
- Do you like driving?
- No.
(The conversation ends.)
Just like you, I don't like it either.
Would you let someone drive?
It's like one of those things.
I have to be the one grilling the meat.
- You know what I mean?
- Yes.
I feel like I have to be the one driving.
(One man malfunctioning next to his role model)
I feel somewhat obligated.
(Once again, the conversation ends.)
I saw a Pirate Ship over here yesterday.
(Changing the subject)
- A Pirate Ship?
- Did you want to ride that too?
Is that so?
There's a small Pirate Ship.
(Embarrassed)
(You Seok gets flustered several times today.)
Last time, we did everything that he wanted to do.
We rode the luge and went on a boat.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
That must've been nice.
Jung Ah and Sun Young said, "Do you really have to do that?"
Anyway, everything ended up being fun.
It was so much fun.
You Seok, did you check the destination?
(Speaking of which,)
(what could be this rock festival?)
(You Seok looks up the destination on GPS.)
- It's in front of the sea.
- It's in front of the sea?
I'm sure it's the mudflats.
Earlier, I saw a sign for a tidal flat experience center.
(A sign for a tidal flat experience center catches You Seok's eye.)
Tidal flat experience centers are the best.
- It won't be an experience for us.
- We have to make money.
- This is survival.
- It's our livelihood.
We need to earn enough to pay for dinner tonight.
- Yes.
- Right.
(Everyone is convinced that they're going to work.)
We must make a lot of money to treat Jung Seok.
We'll make him delicious food.
- I want to buy him beef.
- It's okay.
(Gasping)
(This whole place is a mudflat.)
- This whole place is a mudflat.
- It's a mudflat.
(Is it a real mudflat in front of them?)
Look over there.
(Stretching out before the siblings)
(With no end in sight)
(A vast, endless tidal flat)
(A massive stage to match the siblings' scale)
(Guests start pour in after hearing about the festival.)
(The front row at the rock festival is mine.)
- We're going into the mudflat.
- This is my first time.
(At last, they arrive at today's festival venue.)
(In front of a fishing co-op building?)
Is there another surprise?
Look over there.
(Surrounded by...)
(all sorts of mysterious equipment with no clear purpose...)
(and suspicious warning signs)
(Then You Seok spots a mysterious banner.)
It's Manila Clam Festival.
(Manila Clam Festival?)
"There's also rock in Manila clams."
"There's also rock in Manila clams?"
(It's finally revealed.)
(The true identity of the rock festival)
(There's rock in pleasure.)
(There's rock in elimination.)
(There's rock in sharing life's ups and downs.)
(There's also rock in Manila clams.)
(Manila clams)
(Welcome to Manila Clam Festival!)
So they meant Manila Clam Festival by a rock festival.
"There's also rock in Manila clams?"
"There's also rock in Manila clams."
- There's also rock in Manila clams.
Of course.
- There's also rock...
- In Manila clams.
(Ready to head to work with a rock and roll spirit?)
My goodness.
Look at that.
The Siblings' Manila Clam Festival.
- Manila Clam.
- It's so funny.
Welcome to Manila Clam Festival.
(Clapping automatically)
Rock and roll.
Could you play some music for us?
Today's catch is Taean Beopsan-ri’s prized specialty,
- premium Manila clams.
- Premium Manila clams?
(The vast mudflats of Beopsan-ri in Taean)
(Named for the soft rustling sound they make when they're shaken)
(Taean's first seasonal ingredient: Manila clams)
(Shaped by the ebb and flow of the tides)
(The pristine mudflats of Geunsoman by the West Sea)
This mudflat is a mix of sand and mud.
(Growing in rich mud)
The Manila clams here are exceptionally hardy.
(Fresh, premium Manila clams with extraordinary vitality)
(They're thriving more than usual as they're in season.)
Come and have some Taean Manila clams.
(Taean Manila clams)
That's amazing.
(I like Manila clams.)
Rock and roll. Look over there.
My gosh.
(Is there something else?)
- Where?
- Look over there.
- What's all that?
- They'll be going into the mudflat.
There are so many.
This is huge.
There are enough people to make it a festival.
(On a scale worthy of a real festival)
(A huge fleet of cultivators)
(But wait...)
(There's no end in sight?)
(Warming up on the mudflat track)
(There's a whole fleet of cultivators.)
(These people waiting in two lines are...)
(the ultimate...)
(Manila clam...)
(chasers...)
(of the West Sea Grand Prix.)
(To claim pole position on the mudflat track,)
(they come to the mudflat early in the morning.)
(They take off on a first-come, first-served basis.)
(Therefore, the drivers line up on the track early in the morning.)
(F1 coming soon)
(F1, as in Mudflat 1, coming soon)
- All right.
- Let's go.
(The siblings changed their clothes, and now they're all set.)
They all must be working together.
I guess we're riding it...
- to go far from here.
- Right.
I can feel the mudflat...
- right through my boots.
- Right.
- Hello.
Hello.
- You look prettier in person.
Thank you so much.
(A passionate welcome)
(Right then, a tractor caught Jung Seok's eyes.)
Go, Taean's Pickled Vegetables!
(Exclaiming with joy)
Our tractor must be quite far.
(After a long, muddy trudge,)
(they finally reached their tractor.)
- Hello, sir.
- Hello.
You can hop on the tractor.
(The sweet You Seok helps Jung Ah jump on the tractor.)
I'm okay. I can do it by myself.
- Oh, my goodness.
- Oh, my.
(Jung Seok jumps on the tractor in his own unique way.)
(And this man here is embarrassed.)
Sit in the front.
(After everything that happened, everyone is on the tractor now!)
- This will be fun.
- Exactly.
Another exciting adventure awaits us today.
Right.
(Everything is ready here.)
(This is the wild mudflat circuit of the West Sea Grand Prix.)
(And the roar of the engines echoes across the mudflat.)
(The tractor engine accelerates,)
(and the Manila clam chasers are ready to go.)
Here we go. Let's go.
(With everything happening at once, Team Siblings is getting nervous.)
(We can't wait any longer.)
All right.
(The time has come.)
(The tide is out.)
(It's time to run.)
Bye.
(Dozens of tractors are charging across the mudflat together.)
(It's a truly spectacular sight.)
(In this Mudflat 1 race,)
(you just feel it.)
(The speed explodes!)
Jung Ah, I'm a little nervous.
It's already exciting.
A lot of tractors are rolling in, lined up over there too.
(Another massive lineup of tractors are rolling in from the other side.)
(It's practically a mudflat race.)
(The Manila clam chasers...)
(let their driving instinct explode.)
(In this wild world of the mudflat,)
(who will emerge as the Manila clam champion?)
Are they coming?
(It won't be them, for sure.)
(Unlike the members, the seniors look calm and peaceful.)
I'm driving slowly right now...
- for you guys.
- I see.
From behind, you would look like...
With this position, I must look like a superhero.
I must look weird, but I can't do anything about it.
- He must look like Spider Man.
- He must look funny.
I am Spider Man...
- because I'm Gummy's husband.
- That makes sense.
- Jung Seok is really...
- I should hold here.
He really looks funny.
Is it incredibly hard to harvest Manila clams?
- No.
- No?
- Is it not hard?
- I'll do it for you.
- Thank you.
- Nice.
- It has to be a secret.
- Please keep it a secret.
Slip us some behind our backs, please.
I think we're going all the way over there.
I think you're right.
I'm grateful we get to ride the tractor.
- Exactly. Imagine we have to walk.
- Right. Me too.
- Right.
- Oh, my.
(Across the mud and through the water)
- I see a lot of seagulls.
- Right.
We're here.
(Finally, they arrived at their working spot!)
Thank you.
- Let's go. Grab your baskets.
- Okay.
Let's go.
(They get off the tractor with a basket for Manila clams.)
Look here. There are Manila clam shells here.
So far, it feels like we're at a mudflat festival.
- It sure is the rock festival.
- The rock festival.
The rock festival.
The chairman here will show you...
how to harvest Manila clams.
- Okay.
- Is the chairman here?
- Chairman Lee, please come.
- Oh, my.
- Hello.
- Oh, my. Hello.
Thank you for coming out in such hot weather.
- That's okay.
- It's nice to meet you.
Isn't it nice to be on the mudflat?
- Yes!
You don't know how to harvest Manila clams, do you?
- No.
- Okay.
You can see the Manila clam eyes on the mud.
These are the Manila clam eyes. Do you see them?
- You mean, the breathing holes?
- Right, the breathing holes.
- You got it right.
- I got it right.
Under those breathing holes, you'll find Manila clams.
- We have to dig there.
- Yes, you have to dig there.
I'll show you. Dig where the holes are, like this.
(The first method of harvesting Manila clams)
(Using a clam hoe, scrape the mud surface...)
(where the breathing holes are.)
(Once you see a Manila clam on the surface,)
(dig around it with a rake.)
You can find the Manila clams.
(Then, a lot more Manila clams will pop out.)
(Pick up the Manila clams.)
(Put them in the strainer.)
Some people dig them out 1 by 1,
- just like I showed you.
- Yes.
And there's another way.
(The second method of harvesting Manila clams)
- Gather the mud like this...
- Yes.
(After raking and gathering the mud...)
Can you hand me that?
Yes, that one. You just have to put it all in here.
(Into the strainer)
- Oh, like that?
- Oh, my.
Put it all in here and...
Then the Manila clams are left in the strainer.
(Shake the strainer, everything else but Manila clams is sifted.)
You can harvest Manila clams in this way as well.
- I prefer this way.
- I like this method.
You can get a lot of them at once.
(Fascinated)
(You can get a lot of them at once.)
- Throw out the empty shells.
- It's no joke.
That's a lot.
See? I just harvested a lot.
(Harvest Manila clams using these two method,)
(with a rake or a strainer)
(Wash them in seawater.)
(Then, shake the strainer to sift out the small ones.)
(Only the ones left in the strainer are approved.)
(Put the approved Manila clams in the basket, and that's it.)
You're allowed to harvest up to 60kg per day.
(Beopsan-ri has a 60kg daily limit per household to protect resources.)
- Did you say 60kg?
- Is it 60kg per household?
- As for the price, - Really?
- it's 3 dollars per kilogram.
- We can harvest up to 60kg?
- Three dollars per kilogram?
- Oh, my.
(That means...)
(Within the 60kg limit, the more they harvest,)
(the more money they will earn.)
(60kg times 3 dollars is 180 dollars.)
(They can get up to 180 dollars.)
(But here's the thing about harvesting Manila clams.)
(You have to rake the mud hundreds of times...)
(with your back bent over before the tide comes in.)
(In this vast mudflat,)
(how many Manila clams will they be able to harvest?)
(Catch me if you can.)
- I see many breathing holes there.
- Yes, those are breathing holes.
- This seems to be a nice spot.
- Yes.
- I see a lot of holes here.
- Okay.
- Can you see the breathing holes?
- Yes.
- Where? What does it look like?
- These are the breathing holes.
(If you look closely at the mudflat...)
(All these holes are breathing holes.)
- Try it. Go ahead.
- Okay.
(Chanting a rhythm)
(As she digs around the breathing holes while chanting a rhythm...)
There are many of them here.
(Manila clams appear every time she rakes.)
(Chanting)
(She puts the mud in her strainer.)
(Shake it.)
(After a mud rain pours through the strainer,)
(it is filled with Manila clams.)
Jung Ah, look at this.
(Proud)
Yoon Seo is good at this.
(Jung Ah, who is harvesting Manila clams using a rake...)
There's a lot here.
- Right?
- Yes.
(She's busy picking up Manila clams.)
(She's in the zone.)
- These Manila clams squirt water.
- Yes?
- That's right. They do.
- Yes.
Manila clams squirt water.
Right.
Oh, my. There's a lot here.
There are tons of them here.
(Manila clams are all over this vast mudflat.)
But I have no idea...
- how many it takes to weigh 60kg.
- You're doing great.
I need to know that so I can pace myself.
Manila clams!
- Chairman Lee.
- Yes?
How much does it weigh when it's completely full?
- When it's full...
- Yes.
It weighs 15kg when you fill this to the brim,
and it weighs 20kg if you pile it up this much above the rim.
(A full basket weighs 15kg.)
- Understood.
- Okay.
(This much weighs 15kg.)
(It's more than you might think.)
- A full basket weighs 15kg?
- A full basket weighs 15kg.
- Okay.
- I just have to fill one basket.
(The siblings' goal is to harvest as many Manila clams as possible.)
We've got this.
(You Seok, who has been harvesting Manila clams using a strainer...)
It's easier to harvest them than I thought it would be.
(He also works hard to harvest Manila clams.)
(His basket is getting filled gradually.)
(He puts the clams he harvested in his basket.)
(You Seok takes Jung Ah's basket to her as she's far from it.)
- Jung Ah.
- Yes?
Here.
- Put them in here.
- Okay.
(As always, the third sibling looks after Jung Ah thoughtfully.)
You harvested a lot.
(Jung Ah, the top-tier worker, harvested a lot in a short time.)
My, this is fun.
(The siblings are excited as they easily find Manila clams.)
This is fun, indeed.
I've only eaten them before. This is a unique experience.
(Jung Seok is excited about doing his first hard work in a mudflat.)
(Getting his hopes up)
(He puts mud in his strainer, just as he was told.)
Is 60kg a lot?
Dear me.
(Hoping for an abundant harvest, he shakes his strainer.)
Darn it.
I worked hard, but I harvested only one.
(Manila clam)
(His first mudflat labor isn't going so smoothly.)
(Meanwhile, You Seok, who is right in front of him,)
(uses the same method as Jung Seok.)
(He puts mud in his strainer.)
(Then he shakes his strainer.)
(A large pile of Manila clam)
(Glancing)
You Seok, you're really good at harvesting clams.
They just keep coming out.
(The Manila clam rocker has found a new talent.)
I mean, when I... Why can't I find them?
Over there?
Should I move near the water?
(But all he found here are empty shells.)
Why... Gosh. Why can't I find them?
Where are those holes? What kind of holes should I find?
Come. Move to your right.
- There's a lot here.
- Oh, to the right.
- Chairman Lee. Thank you.
- Are there many clams there?
Bring your baskets over here.
- Follow me. This spot is a jackpot.
- Should we all move over there?
Where?
(We can't miss out on a jackpot!)
A jackpot? Guys, let's go and hit a jackpot.
This spot is a jackpot.
- He's already harvested a lot.
- Impressive.
This is the bare minimum.
- You're amazing, You Seok.
- This spot is a jackpot.
- Pardon?
- You're incredible.
Well, I'm quite dexterous.
(You Seok, the Manila clam ace)
(Everyone moves to another spot in search of a jackpot.)
You're the ace.
Look. Manila clams are lying around on the mud.
(As vast as the mudflat is, it's packed with many Manila clams.)
- There are many holes around here.
- Where?
- Oh, like this one?
- Here. This is a breathing hole.
- It's a breathing hole. Yes.
- Like this one?
- These are all Manila clams.
- Okay.
(Just a few steps away, they found so many breathing holes.)
(They dig the spot that the chairman led them to.)
- Oh, my. I found a lot.
- Right. You found a lot.
(Jung Seok is getting a great harvest too.)
You see, these Manila clams...
Mudflats are packed with nutrients, you know.
(Mudflats are called the kidneys of the sea as it purifies the sea.)
The mudflat is rich in nutrients like calcium, potassium, and sodium,
and Manila clams feed on those.
(And Manila clams that feed on the mud packed with nutrients...)
So they're rich in iron...
and some other nutrients.
- They're a good hangover cure.
- A hangover cure?
- We should eat a lot of them.
- I need these clams.
- Oh, my. Really?
- It helps with a hangover.
There's a ton here.
(Huddled together, they're hunting for the local specialties.)
They just come out whenever I rake.
Guys, have you picked up the pace?
- Yes!
- Yes, it's going really well.
- It's no joke.
- It's going well.
That's good.
(And here, someone is more into it than anyone else.)
I don't even have to walk away. They're just everywhere.
My goodness. Look at this. They just keep coming out.
They just come out every time I rake.
I don't even have to wander around.
(As always, she's working hard with both her hands and her mouth.)
Viewers, we've come here to harvest Manila clams.
Have you been doing well...
this past month? They just come out so easily.
(Kim Sun Young's Mudflat with Manila Clams)
Let me show you from my body cam's point of view.
They come out easily, right?
Viewers, you've never seen this before, right? Like this.
If you rake the mud like this, you'll get Manila clams.
Do you see these Manila clams here?
My goodness. This is fascinating.
Sun Young, are you starting to mumble to yourself again?
(While Sun Young is communicating with the viewers...)
They come out with a single rake.
They come out with just a single rake.
Watch this. They're coming out with a single rake.
(Jung Seok started having fun at the spot he moved to.)
This is fun.
It's fun.
(Jung Seok, the great harvester)
- This...
- Manila clams...
- Yoon Seo.
- Yes?
Isn't it good to be on this show?
- The girls are nice to you and all.
- I was born to be on this show.
- Right?
- I'm serious.
I think that's the case.
The two of us enjoy every moment filming this show.
Jung Ah's food is really good.
And when do I ever get to experience something like this?
That sounds good.
It's an experience you can't buy with money.
(With one shared goal,)
(the siblings pour their sweat into digging up Manila clams.)
Okay. Let's put them in the basket.
Let's put them in the basket.
(30 minutes have passed since the harvest began.)
So, we're making money from this...
and having Manila clam kalguksu later, Captain Yum?
No, I had it all planned out the moment I saw these clams.
- Oh, Manila clams! Olio e aglio!
- I'll do it. Thank you.
- No, I'm going to...
- "Olio e aglio?"
Olio e aglio, the dish made with Manila clams, you know?
(It's vongole.)
No, I'm going to...
(The dinner menu Planner Yum has in mind is...)
I'm going to make jjamppong for a change.
- With Manila clams? Sounds tasty.
- Jjamppong? Sounds good.
I'm going to make jjamppong.
That will be so delicious.
Let's make a lot of money from this...
- to buy other kinds of seafood.
- Right.
Let's do that!
(He's excited at the thought of Manila clam jjamppong.)
If we...
harvest enough clams to hit our goal,
we'll receive 180 dollars?
- That's correct.
- We'll get 180 dollars?
Each of us must harvest 12kg of Manila clams.
- That's right. We can do it.
- Each has to harvest 12kg?
Would 90 dollars be not enough to make it?
- No, that wouldn't be enough.
- Of course not.
- Is that right?
- Yes.
We won't just have jjamppong. We'll have tangsuyuk too.
Oh, my. That sounds delicious.
Jung Ja, do you like tangsuyuk?
I can't get enough of it.
(He loves tangsuyuk.)
Really? To make tangsuyuk, we'll need some pork...
(I should work busily!)
(Jjamppong...)
(and tangsuyuk)
(Let's eat both.)
(Sun Young turned on the booster and is moving so fast.)
(Groaning)
To earn 180 dollars.
We should make tangsuyuk for Jung Ja since he came from Seoul today.
I must work hard.
I must work hard so that we can get 180 dollars.
(Let's not forget. The more clams we harvest, the more money we earn!)
I must work hard.
Where are breathing holes?
Breathing holes.
Breathing holes? I found them.
(She charges forward once she spots breathing holes.)
Oh, I see a lot of them here.
There are many breathing holes here.
(Yoon Seo, the breathing hole hunter)
There's a lot here.
(Once Yoon Seo settles in and starts digging into the mud...)
They're just swept up by a single rake.
(The mudflat is wiped out.)
Here it is.
(Clenching her teeth)
Breathing holes.
(Breathing heavily)
(It's heavy, but she squeezes out her strength to shake the strainer.)
I can do it. I can fill this up.
(Step by step, her basket is filling up.)
(While the optimistic Yoon Seo feels the joy of harvesting clams...)
I'm so good at this. I'm amazing.
- You've harvested a lot.
- Yes.
- You see...
- Yes?
I've been on this show for three years.
- Oh, really?
- So I'm good at almost everything.
(Her confidence comes from her experience.)
You're so good at this. You look like you're weeding a field.
Jung Ah, please give me some tips.
Well, I just dug them up. That's all.
(Unlike what she said,)
(she keeps moving her hands at the same spot without a break.)
(Raking like crazy)
There's nothing left here.
- You've harvested a lot.
- Yes, I have.
(Her speed impresses the original Manila clam rocker.)
This is my third batch.
(It's already her third batch.)
(It's quite a huge pile.)
I don't even have to rake twice.
- Look at this. My goodness.
- I can do this, right?
(The siblings are harvesting clams in their own ways.)
- I hit a jackpot. This is a lot.
- I can do this.
- I can do this. I've got this.
- Oh, my.
- Yoon Seo, is it going well?
- Well...
- I'm not sure.
- This is amazing.
- Oh, there's a lot here.
- Picking them up is way faster.
- It's faster for us.
- Exactly.
They just keep coming out.
(Groaning)
(Her stool is stuck in the mud.)
(Laughing)
I can't get up.
(Stretching)
(What is that?)
You can't get up.
- It's hard to get up.
- It's not like that.
I'm stuck in the mud.
- What?
- Her stool is stuck in the mud.
(She became one with the mudflat.)
(Flustered)
Wait. I'll come to you.
(The two of them end up going to rescue her.)
(We're coming to rescue you.)
- Goodness, you.
- All I did was...
- work hard.
- She's completely stuck in the mud.
- I can't get up. Oh, thank you.
- Oh, gosh.
I just heard a popping sound.
- The mud is totally caved in.
- Hold on a second.
You must've sat there for so long seeing that you got stuck there.
(Sun Young left a legendary mark on the mudflat.)
Exactly. She must've sat in the same spot for so long.
Gosh, it's so heavy. I put too much in here.
(The biggest problem is...)
I put too much in here.
(The mud, soaked with water, is heavier than they expected.)
(The more they put in, the heavier it gets.)
Just...
making simple soup with these... My back hurts.
(On top of that, they have to stay bent over to dig up the clams.)
Gosh, I might end up with a hunched back at this rate.
(Staggering)
(Sitting down for so long, his legs gave up.)
Dear me.
(The siblings are starting to get tired.)
Jung Ah, this is hard.
Indeed. But there's no easy job in this world.
(There's no easy job in this world, but...)
(With no shade in this vast mudflat,)
(digging up hidden Manila clams is no easy feat.)
(What you need when you're getting tired is...)
One lighting under a dim light
It's "one candle."
- Oh, is it "candle?" - It's "candle."
Reflected on the wine glass is
- The world of Manila clams - A promise
The world of Manila clams
Many people choose this song for their wedding.
I'm sure a lot of people sing it at a wedding.
Jung Seok, have you sung at many weddings?
I've sung at a few weddings.
- They must've been so happy.
- I sang "Aloha."
- People must've loved hearing it.
- Exactly.
Even the guests.
Right?
- I...
- Can you sing a song at my wedding?
Here's...
(She's been married for 17 years.)
Here's an interesting story.
There was this producer I used to work with.
He asked me to sing at his wedding.
Back then, I had just gotten vision correction surgery.
I couldn't see anything and was told to keep my eyes closed.
Oh, dear.
I introduced Gummy instead.
You introduced Gummy?
When I did, the producer said, "Nice!"
(All the better)
He was over the moon.
(The ultimate wedding singer)
"Nice?"
Maybe he was actually after Gummy.
Yes, that's a possibility.
He couldn't ask Gummy himself.
- Of course not.
- He might come across as rude.
(A lively chat unfolds on the mudflat.)
- Goodness.
- This is fun.
(Optimistic Yoon Seo)
Isn't it fun?
- It is.
- Why...
Chatting makes it fun.
(Talking makes the hard work feel a little easier.)
How joyful.
Hey, Seok's dad. It's been a while...
since I last saw you here.
Sun Young.
- What?
- I'm Jung Ja.
A woman, okay?
Despite my husky voice.
- Were you a woman?
- Jung Ja, is it?
I didn't know.
Are you Jung Ja, not Seok's dad?
Jung Ja, do you still shave?
If only I had less hair, you know?
(Laughing)
It's impossible not to shave.
You Soon, you used to follow...
Jung Ja around all the time.
- Why are you being awkward now?
- Exactly. Didn't you miss her?
Why are you so quiet now that she's here?
- It's been a while, okay?
- She's all nervous.
- Exactly. I'm getting shy.
- Gosh.
I'm ready, okay?
(Jung Ja's sudden flirtation)
- Is your heart ready for me?
- Of course.
(The flirting game begins)
(You Soon realizes Jung Ja's feelings.)
Well, I'll see you later in the evening. Okay?
My gosh, how naughty.
- Two women in the evening?
- "Naughty?"
(You Soon only has eyes for Jung Ja.)
(Jung Ja doesn't hate it all that much.)
You must give me your number. Got it, You Soon?
(Getting shy)
- Can I?
- Go ahead.
"Can I?"
(Flirting flying left and right, this is "Mudflat Island.")
(Raking)
(Splashing)
(It's already been 1.5 hours since digging up Manila clams.)
(Raking slows to a crawl)
(Suddenly much quieter)
(Groaning)
My wrist hurts.
My back is killing me.
(Out of battery)
Is there any way to keep my back from hurting?
(The camera moves to get a good shot of Sun Young.)
Why are you suddenly rushing in on me?
For what?
(The camera moves to get a good shot of Sun Young.)
Why are you suddenly rushing in on me?
For what?
Didn't you stay far away earlier?
Why come when I'm lying down and not when I was working hard?
Get a shot of me working hard,
not when I'm taking a short break.
Really, the viewers will get the wrong idea.
Seriously, these people.
(Like a press conference)
They come swarming in on me.
I'm going to work hard!
I was working hard like this, you know?
(Working after a 10-second break)
(Back to digging with renewed energy)
- Take a break, Sun Young.
- What?
Take a break.
You should too, Jung Ah. Are you okay?
I don't know what taking a break is.
You should learn, Jung Ah.
My goodness.
(Even Captain Yum is running on empty...)
(after hours of backbreaking work.)
Oh, gosh. I'm tired.
This is tough.
(Glancing)
My leg hurts.
(Everyone is drained.)
How about we all take a break?
Should we take a break and play a game here on the mudflat?
What?
Should we take a break and play a game?
What kind of game do you have in mind?
Let's bet on something...
and play a game with these guys.
- What game?
- With the production staff?
Yes.
(The gamer puts on his thinking cap.)
Long jump?
(How about mudflat long jump?)
Let's do long jump.
Mudflat long jump.
As You Seok suggested,
how about a match of long jump?
Right here?
I'm in!
Okay!
If the five of you can jump...
a total of more than 5m, we'll give you 50 dollars.
- What?
- A total of 5m?
- Each has to jump 1m?
- The 5 of us?
Okay.
How do we pass 5m?
I doubt I can even jump 30cm.
How about we add ten dollars...
for every additional 1m you jump?
(10 dollars for every 1m?)
Nice.
(The production staff's shocking offer)
- Okay, 5m. Let's do it.
- Okay.
- So we get 50 dollars for 5m.
- And then 10 dollars per 1m.
- We can totally do it.
- Great.
- I'm taking my hat off.
Let's do this.
- Okay, let's go.
- We only have to jump 1m each.
- Let's go for it.
- Okay.
- Can we practice?
- Jump 5m, and we get 50 dollars.
Okay.
(The 1st Siblings' Mudflat Long Jump Competition)
That's the jump line.
This is the starting line.
You have to jump from here, the run-up spot.
Here. It's best to keep the run-up area hard.
The mud is so wet.
(Light splashing)
(Following You Seok)
(Extremely determined)
- Good luck, Jung Ah.
- First. I'm going to jump.
- Okay.
- First jumper.
Good luck, Yum Jung Ah!
(Jumping line)
- Good luck.
- Let's go!
- Okay!
- Nice.
- Good luck!
- Let's go!
(Jumping lightly)
(After landing safely)
(An ending pose)
(Jung Ah's record)
It's 1.10m.
He said 1.10m.
(She passed 1m!)
Let's try for 60 dollars!
- Good job.
- Nice.
- You did your share.
- We could go for 60 dollars.
- We totally could.
- Second.
Second jumper.
Kim Sun Young, 51 years old.
- Good luck, Kim Sun Young!
- Let's go!
Go!
(Jumping line)
- Okay!
- Nice.
(Okay!)
- You two are good at it.
- Sun Young...
No, measure up...
to my heel.
- You stepped here.
- No.
- The end of the body is...
- I'll measure from here.
Come on, sir.
- Who is he?
- Gosh. You're harsh.
Aren't you...
- Who are you? Aren't we a family?
- mean?
- This is...
- Be a little nice.
Are you from an international organization?
- This isn't some...
- Are you a judge?
Are you certified?
It's 1.20m.
- He said 1.20m.
- It's still over 1m.
- What if I jump like 50cm?
- Here.
(Records, Total: 2.12m)
- Who...
- The rising star,
- Who is next? Me?
- Roh Yoon Seo.
- Introduce yourself.
- Third, Roh Yoon Seo!
- Okay.
- Wait, Yoon Seo!
Where do you plan on stepping off?
Sun Young!
Where are you going to step?
- I won't.
- That spot looks good.
- Step here, okay?
- Okay.
- Should I lie down over there?
- Stop.
(Packing the mud down)
(Feeling the pressure)
One, two.
(Will she jump far?)
(Jumping line)
- That was far.
- Yoon Seo jumped more than 1m.
She didn't step on the line, right?
Amazing, Yoon Seo!
(Well done, youngest!)
- It's 1.66m.
- What?
- Incredible.
- That's my height.
How did you jump so far?
Great job.
Amazing.
- We can do it.
- Yes, 3.70m.
You Seok, go last.
- Apparently, 5m was too short.
- Right?
They should've suggested 7m.
- Exactly.
- Yes.
- Isn't it 70 dollars if we jump 7m?
(Laughing)
How dare you look down on us!
(Dancing)
Fourth, Cho Jung Seok.
(Jumping line)
Unbelievable.
- Unbelievable.
He flew. Jung Seok literally flew.
(Here's a replay of Jung Seok the Flyer.)
(Hup!)
(A quick grunt, followed by a smooth landing)
(Did you see that?)
It's 1.99m.
(Jung Seok's record: 1.99m)
- My gosh.
- Good.
You could even join the Summer Games.
- That was no joke.
- For real.
Was it 1.99m?
(The only jumper left)
Am I the last? The pressure.
I don't think I can jump 2m.
- Here I go.
- Okay.
(5th jumper, Kang You Seok)
(The farther You Seok jumps, the more money gets added!)
Go slow at first.
(Jumping line)
(What a good jump!)
(It was indeed a good jump, but...)
Okay.
- His hand.
- Hand?
- No.
- No, I didn't land on my hand.
(Not a chance.)
You jumped more than enough.
(You Seok jumped far even if he used his hand.)
It's 1.88m.
- Amazing.
- Cool, You Seok.
It would've been 2m...
- if he hadn't used his hand.
- You jumped the farthest.
- We get 70... No, 80 dollars.
- It was his hand.
(Records, Total: 7.65m)
(The 5 jumped a total of 7.65m.)
- The total is 7.65m.
- Is it 76.5 dollars?
That'll be 76...
- Give us 76.52 dollars.
- It's 76.5 dollars.
Seventy...
(Earned another 20 dollars from a bonus game)
I spinned. You saw me spin, right?
Great job, everyone.
- Okay.
- Okay, thank you.
- Let's go.
- Yes, let's get going.
- Let's work.
- Hurry.
(Let's dig up more clams before the tide comes in!)
(The siblings are back to digging up clams after a sweet break.)
(Raking as fast as before thanks to the break)
(The second is practically getting sucked into the mudflat.)
I spot many here. Yes!
I'm tired.
No, I'm not.
(Losing it)
I'm not tired.
This may look easy.
But look, the clams are deep down.
The sun is rising.
It's rising just as we'll be leaving soon.
(As if the work wasn't hard enough,)
(the sun is scorching hot.)
It's hard, isn't it?
At least you're young with muscles.
Oh, dear.
(The clams show up after repeated digging.)
(Get as much as possible before the tide comes in!)
It's tiring.
I want to see how the experts dig up the clams.
- Right, Sun Young?
- I wonder how fast they are.
(Curious about the experts' speed)
I can see them from here.
They're no joke.
(Even from afar, it's obvious their speed is on another level.)
(Shall we take a look at the Manila clam seniors?)
(With speed on another level)
(Years of experience show in every rake)
(This is the strength of the seniors.)
This isn't an easy job.
Anyone would do it if it were easy.
Oh, gosh. I wonder how the ladies dig them up so well.
(Appreciating the seniors' hard work even more)
They're amazing.
Those ladies are incredible. I'm serious.
I didn't know clam digging was this hard.
I will eat them with appreciation now.
For real.
I will devour the clams in the Manila clam kalguksu.
Digging for them is hard.
(Every clam is a labor of love.)
(After carefully digging the clams up)
- Will the tide come in soon?
- Yes, it's already coming in.
(Not much time left before the tide returns)
- Already?
- Yes.
- Guys.
- Hurry.
We've got to dig up at least another kilogram.
- Three dollars.
- I've hit a jackpot here!
- A jackpot.
I'm going over, okay?
(Let's go for the last spurt!)
Oh, my.
It's heavy, isn't it?
This spot is filled with holes.
(All five speed it up.)
Okay.
Since it's a drop shipment,
- the clams we dig up...
- Exactly.
will be sold somewhere, and the viewers will make...
- Manila clam kalguksu out of them.
- Yes.
- Even make doenjang jjigae.
- Like so.
Here. Premium Manila clams.
See this?
Two, three, four.
When will I ever experience this?
It will become a legacy, an asset,
and a life experience.
The roots, the seeds, and the tree.
Eventually, an apple and an apple pie.
(Driving by)
(Lost in the work,)
(the tractors head home one by one.)
The tractors are starting up one by one.
(The tractors leaving mean...)
(the tide will come in any time soon.)
(We should also go back to land.)
(The siblings gather to weigh the clams.)
(Splitting the clams into bags)
All done.
Remember I said it was three dollars per kilogram?
Yes.
(Weighing the first bag)
It's 10kg.
(The 1st bag weighs 9.6kg.)
(The second bag weighs...)
It's 8.2kg.
(8.2kg.)
- This one is the heaviest.
- How much in total?
These are the first clams I dug up.
How heavy is it?
Is it 20kg?
Take your hands off the bag, please.
- Sorry?
- Stop with the dirty tricks.
(The scale drops as soon as he lets go.)
- It's 12.6kg.
- Right?
(The 3rd bag is 12.6kg.)
(Done digging up at a total of 30.4kg)
- How much is it?
- Three times three is nine.
- Is it 90 dollars?
- It's 90 dollars.
- That just now was...
- Ninety dollars.
How much is the grand total?
It's 180 dollars.
Really?
Imagine the amount...
- Sun Young...
- if we hadn't played long jump.
I thought 60kg of clams would be easy peasy.
We can't possibly dig up 60kg.
- Exactly.
- It sure is tough.
That wouldn't have cut it.
- Thank you!
- Thank you.
You had it tough in the heat.
- Did you earn a lot?
- Yes.
- Thank you.
Clean clams for you to eat. After all, they're in season.
Can we eat them right away?
- Yes.
- Thank you.
- They've already been purged.
- Really?
- Thank you.
- We can eat them right away.
(Purged Manila clams will be served today.)
It feels pretty rewarding to have dug up that many clams.
(Staring)
Look at all those holes.
- All I can see are the holes.
- Right?
Those are all siphon openings.
Mudflats are tough.
- My legs are starting to give way.
- Right?
My back and hands took quite a beating.
- We're back on land.
- We're here.
(They arrived on land before they knew it.)
The clams are cleaned immediately over here.
(Right next to where the tractors come in)
(The clam washing and sorting station)
(The clams we harvested today are...)
(washed and sorted by size here.)
(Squeaky clean)
(Packed into 20kg bags,)
(the fresh clams are...)
(shipped straight to destinations across the country.)
(The siblings wash off the mud at the tap.)
(His mischievous face says it all.)
(Annoyed)
(2nd time)
(3rd time)
(Are you trying me?)
(Here's my revenge!)
(Monkey mode on)
(A full-scale water fight breaks out.)
(For a moment, they're kids again.)
(A water fight is enough to make these siblings happy.)
Oh, gosh.
(Feeling happy just by watching them)
How young.
You sure are young.
This is fun. A water fight is fun.
(The siblings cooled down with a water fight.)
I'm sleepy. I need to fill in my brows.
(After digging up the clams)
(Spotted the camera)
Dear viewers, we're not one bit tired.
We're back after a shower.
You see my bare brows? A shocker, right?
(The viewers are Sun Young's energizer.)
Let's check my brows.
I'm not sure if I can fill them in...
when the car is moving.
Before filling in my brows,
- let's apply something to my face.
- Seventeen minutes.
- That's plenty of time.
Seventeen minutes.
Yoon Seo, let's make a list of the groceries to buy.
- List the groceries?
- Yes.
- Okay.
- Our grocery list.
Got it.
Meat for tangsuyuk.
- Cucumbers. We need cucumbers.
- Give me a second.
- Cucumbers.
Meat for tangsuyuk.
- Pork sirloin.
- Meat for tangsuyuk.
Jjamppong.
Seafood.
- We only have Manila clams.
- Seafood.
And then, let's move on to pepper japchae.
- Okay.
- Gosh.
- Pepper japchae sounds good.
- Right?
- Flower buns.
We need flower buns.
(A spectacular Chinese feast is coming soon.)
Bell peppers, onions, and you wrote that down, right?
Let's buy zucchini and button mushrooms if there are any.
- Okay.
They're good inside jjamppong.
Let's play Word Chain. Zucchini.
- Ni, Jung Ah.
- Ni?
(All of a sudden?)
Five, four, three, two, one.
- Bye.
- What's there with an "Ni?" - Nice.
- Three syllables?
- Two or three?
Three. We'll go clockwise, starting with Jung Ah.
- It's Jung Seok after me.
- Okay.
- You can't say nice.
- Restart.
- No nice.
- Come on.
(Officially starting Word Chain)
- Shall we do it in Chinese?
- What?
Chinese?
(Officially starting Chinese Word Chain)
I only know "xiexie."
(Speaking gibberish)
What is that?
- Only the intonation is in Chinese.
- Correct.
- Chinese intonation?
- Here's how you do it.
If I say "wo shi ah," Jung Ah has to start with...
"ah." Go ahead.
"Ah ye."
"Ye?"
Ye he le.
Confidence is what you need.
Yes, confidence.
Let's try it.
You start, Jung Ah.
(Speaking fake Chinese)
Huo la ha yi.
"Yi." Start with an "yi."
Yi er san.
(Nice one!)
San cha ho yi.
"Yi." It's "yi" again.
Yi hong shi.
- "Shi?" - "Shi."
Shi pea ker.
- Isn't that an alien language?
- That just now..
- That sounded Korean.
- That's English.
- No.
- Out.
- It made sense, so bye.
- Hold on.
If it makes sense, you're out.
(Do it properly.)
Let's stop here.
Now, let's move on to Japan.
- Japan.
- I'm confident in that.
- I'm confident.
- I can really do Japanese.
But you can't speak actual Japanese.
- Really?
- Fake Japanese...
but make it sound real.
- Then I'm in a bind.
- Okay.
You can start.
Imakano.
- That was good.
- Imakano.
- Imakano was good.
- "No."
Nogodouri...
- Nogodouri.
Yorushikare.
Why is a word so long? That's a sentence.
Norikashine.
- Omashai...
- Norikashine.
- Omagaishine.
- I can't draw my eyebrows...
because he's so funny.
I can't draw one side of my eyebrows because I'm laughing.
- Omagaisa. "Sa." - "Sa."
(His speech has finally ended.)
- Saichi.
- What is it again?
- "Chi." - Chi?"
Chikino meogo sipo.
- You want to eat fried chicken?
You can't speak Korean.
I thought I just needed to avoid speaking actual Japanese.
Say it again.
- Chikino meogo sipo.
- You want to eat fried chicken?
I'll let it slide once.
- Is it "po?" - "Po."
"Po."
(Po?)
Porigato.
- Arigato?
- I said porigato!
Porigato.
(Denying it to the grave)
"To."
(She continues the game as if nothing happened.)
(Look at her.)
(You're a lunatic.)
(Found guilty)
(Jung Ah-chan once again ends the game.)
(Sun Young is eliminated.)
Let's do Russian.
- Let's play it one last time.
- You sure?
- Russian or French?
- Sun Young. Then can I...
I have a question.
- When will you draw your eyebrow?
- My eyebrow.
- Draw when the car has stopped.
- You're right.
- We're almost there.
- I need to draw this side too.
My eyebrows are uneven.
It's okay.
It's a traditional market.
- That's where we're going?
- Yes.
"Taean Seobu Market."
(As they laugh and talk, they arrive at the market.)
- What's this?
- Small octopus.
They're as big as normal octopus.
Look at the razor shell.
(Octopus-like huge small octopuses to gigantic razor shells)
(As expected of Taean, a maritime city,)
(it's full of fresh seafood.)
(They have freshly-dug Manila clams too.)
It's pretty big.
(From an old-fashioned hair salon...)
(to snacks)
(The traditional market feels very friendly and cozy.)
- You Seok.
- Yes?
I have eyebrows now. Look.
You got prettier.
(Her eyebrows are ready in time.)
(Expectant)
- Sea squirt.
- Hello.
Hello. Manila clams.
Sea squirts.
Wild sea squirts.
(Sea squirts they met in Tongyeong)
The cuttlefish looks so cute.
My gosh.
(The market is full of fascinating and delicious things.)
- Shall we eat that?
- Shall we eat street food?
- Let's eat fishcake and tteokbokki.
- Hello.
- Let's eat first.
- Let's eat.
- I can't walk past this.
- This is so...
- I want a corn dog.
- A corn dog?
I want fishcake.
- Deep-fried squid and gimmari too.
- Okay.
One deep-fried vegetable too.
Give us one plate of tteokbokki too, please.
Please give us a lot.
(She drinks the fishcake soup while waiting for the food.)
The soup is really good.
The soup is so good. My gosh.
(Surprised)
(Amazed)
(The addictive taste never fails you.)
Now that I've tasted the soup, I want to eat fishcake too.
I should eat one.
Thank you.
It's good.
(Enough with the appetizer, the real deal starts now.)
(Humming)
Guys, eat this.
(Eating tteokbokki hurriedly)
(She's amazed by the taste.)
(Getting out of control)
I can't stop eating.
(Taking another bite)
- It's good, right?
- Yes.
It's delicious.
It's so delicious.
(Happy)
I know him.
- Gummy. His wife is Gummy.
- That's right.
- I used to like Gummy.
- Thank you.
- This...
- I like Gummy too.
(Laughing)
Gummy's husband first.
Thank you.
It's freshly deep-fried.
(Crunchy)
(Thanks to Gummy's husband, they get to enjoy it all the more.)
It's so good but hot.
- It's so good.
- Yes.
This deep-fried squid is on the house.
- Gosh, thank you.
- Thank you.
I should give one for Gummy's husband.
Thank you.
I'm Cho Jung Seok, sir.
As much as I am Gummy's husband.
I wanted to tell you.
(Laughing)
- Hope your business flourishes.
- Thank you.
- It's all seafood here.
- There's a lot of seafood.
(Now that we've eaten well, let's go grocery shopping.)
- Goodness.
- My gosh.
- It's big.
- Amazing.
(They buy a gigantic small octopus which will go into jjamppong.)
It looks good.
(They buy more than enough meat for tangsuyuk and japchae too.)
- Hello.
- Do you go to supermarkets often?
- Yes, I do.
It was a long day, wasn't it?
- Today?
- Yes.
- No, today wasn't bad. I had fun.
- Mudflat...
Is this supposed to follow a certain concept?
- Yes, we have a concept.
- Oh, you do.
- Today's concept is...
- Yes.
"Who is Cho Jung Seok? Who is he?"
- "Who is he?" - Yes.
I'm Gummy's husband.
Really?
I'm filming "Who is Cho Jong Seok?"
Excuse me, but I'm not Cho Jong Seok.
I'm Cho Jung Seok.
- It's my pronunciation issue.
- Last time...
Cho Jung Seok.
Cho Jong Seok.
You have one lighting turned on...
under a dim light, right?
- It's one candle.
- Oh, candle.
You're terrible, producer.
You know nothing about me.
Can you ask him about his new song?
- New song...
- If you're going to interview him?
"A River Flowing Backward?"
- What was it?
- Sun Young.
(Laughing)
Oh. "In This Not-Special World, I'm Happy That I Met You."
"I'm Happy."
"In My Life Which Nothing Is Special."
Wrong.
- "In My Not-Special Life." - No. "In My Not-Special Life."
- "Nothing Special." - "Nothing Special."
"My Life."
- Wrong.
- It's "World."
- "In This World." - Wrong.
- "In My Ordinary Life." - "A River Doesn't Flow Backward."
- Hold on.
- "To The Ordinary Me."
- I think he got confused.
- "In This World..."
- "Where Nothing Is Special," - He's getting confused.
- Hold on.
- "I'm Glad I Met You."
- Even the singer is confused.
- Okay.
It was similar.
- "You Changed World." - Yes, that's right.
This is how we feel today.
- Thank you.
- I'm glad you're the first guest...
on the first day here.
- That's great, I like it.
- Thank you.
- Let's go.
"Who is Cho Jong Seok?"
It sounds like Cho Jong Seok to me.
He's Cho Jong Seok.
("Who is Cho Jong Seok" ends on a friendly note.)
Will we finally go, get settled, and eat?
Let's take out the flowers first.
Gosh, it's so pretty.
- He likes that.
- I bought what looked like you.
A...
They should've heard you say this.
- Jung Seok.
- You can go.
I said the flowers were pretty,
and he said, "I bought what looked like you."
That's a good one.
You're witty.
(No wonder his role model is Jung Seok.)
We haven't gone...
- to our house yet, right?
- No.
- We haven't.
- What time is it now?
- This is...
- It's 3:30pm, and we're not home.
- No.
- We haven't gone home.
(How will their Taean house look like?)
I can't wait to find out.
- We're eight minutes away.
- Yes.
- It's far.
- As we sang.
(As they get closer, they become more excited.)
I think the house is on a mountain instead of by the seaside.
Look at all the fields.
We're going toward the mountain, not the sea.
- I like places like this.
- Me too.
- You like stuff like this.
- I love it.
The fields are pretty.
(They drive in between the fields.)
- This road. Here we are.
- To the right.
We're here.
(They're right in front of the house.)
My gosh.
(Looking forward to it)
(The car drives deeper into the mountain.)
(If we go up here...)
(surprised)
(Impressed)
- I love it.
- It's the typical countryside home.
(A familiar red-roofed house which they can see...)
(if they drive up the narrow path)
- It's so nice.
- It has a car park.
(Impressed)
Amazing.
- So cool.
- No way.
- Thank you for driving.
- It's nothing.
- Thank you.
- Thanks, Jung Seok.
My pleasure.
It's so pretty.
Yes.
- It's so pretty.
- My gosh. This is...
(Surprised)
- What's that?
- It's so pretty here.
- It's so pretty.
- Yes.
This is amazing.
(A cozy countryside home with a big yard)
It's so pretty.
This is perfect for me.
- It's so pretty.
(At the foot of the snug mountain,)
(the house is located with the fields as its neighbors.)
(In the yard full of wild flowers,)
(you can enjoy the peaceful views of the fields.)
- I love places like this.
- It's so pretty.
I love it.
Inside.
(After enjoying the yard, they enter the house.)
- My gosh.
- It's so pretty. What's that?
- What's this?
- Another yard.
We'll meet here?
(Another yard in the middle of the house)
(A cozy courtyard too)
We can eat here.
(The house will be filled with excitement.)
This is so nice here.
I agree.
(It has many pretty yards.)
(Siblings' Flower Garden House in Taean)
- I can't believe this.
- Amazing.
(What exciting events await us here?)
(She spots a piano on one side.)
They have a piano too.
- Do you play the piano?
- I do.
I'm no joke.
(Pretty stable)
The piano is so pretty. Look at its color.
It's so pretty.
It matches your pants.
The piano has such a pretty color.
(Is the color tailored for its player?)
They have a classical guitar too!
It's an acoustic guitar.
Is that so?
Isn't it a classical guitar?
No, it's acoustic.
- They're different?
- Yes. This is an acoustic guitar.
I wouldn't know all that.
(Jung Seok playing the guitar!)
I haven't played in so long, so I forgot most of it.
You say that,
- but you'll be awesome at it.
- No.
It's so nice.
How nice.
(Fully enjoying the vibe in the front yard)
(A satisfied sigh)
It's so nice.
It's wide-open here.
Where are the neighbors?
(The huge field is right next to the house, like a neighbor.)
(It has various crops growing.)
I want to live here.
(He enjoys the peace in the yard.)
Let's go ride an ATV.
- Are we going right away?
- Right away?
(ATV out of nowhere?)
(Once again, Magnet Kang looked up the things he could do in advance.)
I'm too tired. We need to rest.
(Unlike before, they don't let him drag them around easily.)
I do want to try it.
- It sounds fun.
- Or...
(Interested)
Is the ATV place near?
(Jung Seok is drawn to the magnet.)
(It can't be like this.)
I really don't want to ride it.
- I really don't want to.
- Me neither.
- Just send those born in the 1980s.
- Yes.
(Born in the 1980s)
He's born in 2000.
We have a 2000-born.
(The person born in 2000 gets excited at the mention of ATV.)
- You Seok.
- Yes?
You guys go ahead.
We'll stay at home.
(We'll arrange the flowers.)
Is Yoon Seo a good driver?
Yoon Seo is good.
Honestly, I want...
to ride it myself.
- Me too.
- Right?
You want to ride it yourself, right? Be honest.
Honestly, yes.
We're all riders.
(Heating up like riders)
- I'm ready to go.
- Okay.
- See you.
- Have fun.
Thanks.
(Trailing behind Magnet Kang)
(Singing Jung Seok's new song to see him off)
(The whole world)
(Is colored by you)
"The moment it's colored!"
The moment it's colored
I never tried it.
- ATV is fun.
- Really?
(She spots an ATV.)
It looks so fun.
It's like "Mad Max."
(Big and heavy tires)
(Bulky body)
(Which course will they drive the wild ATVs?)
(It's next to both a mountain and a sea,)
(which makes our town, Sindu-ri, beautiful.)
(It's a course which stops by the popular spots.)
(It passes by the siblings' house halfway.)
(Shall we?)
(Wearing the helmet tightly)
Okay.
(They're ready to go.)
The camera is "Music Bank" style.
(Trying to win)
Okay.
(A cool pose here too)
We're like "KartRider."
(We're like "KartRider.")
(Crazy Racing Siblings Rider)
(Host: 5 More Minutes, Mom)
(He gets everything he wants by whining.)
(He suggested this game too.)
(Uncle Cho Jong Seok)
(Even his name suggests he is a driver.)
(He doesn't plan to go easy on the kids.)
(Yoon Not Going Slow)
(A rider who enjoys speed)
(She doesn't slow down, and she can't drift.)
(Difficulty: 3 out of 5, Sindu-ri sightseeing course)
(Host, ready, game start)
When do we stop posing?
(Laughing)
(Ready)
(Start)
(1st place, Uncle Cho Jong Seok)
(2nd place, Host, 5 More Minutes, Mom)
(Yoon Not Going Slow, rider view)
(Excited)
(1st place, Uncle Cho Jong Seok, 2nd place, 5 More Minutes, Mom)
(3rd place, Yoon Not Going Slow)
This is fun.
(Glancing)
This is insane.
(Childish You doesn't want to lose.)
(He tries to take over.)
(Follow me if you can.)
(1st place, Uncle Cho Jong Seok)
(Vroom)
(The fierce battle between two kids)
(3rd place, Yoon Not Going Slow)
Hello. I'm off.
(Rider in last place drives slowly, regardless of the award.)
It's so fun.
Isn't it so fun?
(3rd place, Yoon Not Going Slow)
I feel so confident.
(Groaning)
(Fully engrossed with her doing it when you can't even them strong)
It's so fun.
(Excited)
(They continue to ride.)
Duwung Wetlands.
It's pretty. Wetlands?
(They arrive at the beautiful wetlands.)
- Duwung Wetlands.
- Duwung.
About 7,000 years ago, this area was a sea.
- I see.
- Until here?
- Yes.
- I see.
- Seven thousand years?
- It formed hills...
and became a wetland.
- It's a natural reserve.
- I see.
(The seawater pooled and became a wetland.)
- There must be a lot of frogs.
- Exactly.
They even have a frog statue.
Gold frog signifies power and wealth.
- Let's touch it.
- Gold frogs.
(You must touch power and wealth.)
Money.
Money is good.
(Laughing)
- Thank you.
(Praying to earn a lot from the next labor)
- Snakes live here too?
- Yes.
Mongolia racerunner?
(It's as good as an ecomuseum.)
- What does it look like?
- Is it as big as salamanders?
Is it like salamanders?
Do you like reptiles?
Me? No, I don't like reptiles.
I think I'll get scared.
- Do you like insects?
- I do like insects.
- Right?
- Gummy.
Spiders aren't insects, though.
I don't like this guy.
Why not?
"It feeds on insects and arachnids."
(It feeds on insects and arachnids.)
How annoying.
It feeds on spiders.
(Laughing)
It shouldn't feed on spiders.
- It should save them.
- They're beneficial insects.
- This is crazy.
- Of course.
- They're beneficial insects.
- My gosh.
Shall we ride faster?
(Done with sightseeing, back to racing mode)
(Sighing)
(Fulfilled by his rage, he's ready to ride.)
(Laughing)
Let's go.
(After sightseeing the wetland,)
(they head to somewhere which is more open.)
It's so pretty.
I feel like I've become the owner...
of a farm with vast fields.
(You Seok, who's only been looking forward to win,)
(glances around.)
They say the richest of them all is the one with the most land.
(Fields spread out on both side of the road.)
It feels like I've become rich in land.
It's like an oreum.
The ridge is so pretty.
It's great for walks too.
(When they drive to the sea, the coastal dune unfolds.)
It's so nice.
(The views that make it hard to believe it's their neighborhood)
(It's nice.)
(As they ride with the beautiful view...)
(Hello.)
Gosh, is that our house?
Is that our house?
(They came to their House.)
Jung Ah!
- Jung Ah!
Hello!
Jung Ah, this is so fun!
(Really?)
It's so fun.
I'd have regretted it if I didn't ride this.
(Magnet Kang's course has 100 percent customer satisfaction.)
That was fun.
(The ATV ride was satisfying.)
It was so fun.
- It was fun.
- I know.
(The youngest looks for Jung Ah and Sun Young.)
(Are they sleeping?)
I didn't sleep.
(I'm not sleeping.)
I couldn't sleep at all.
- Sun Young...
- She passed out.
- Really?
- I couldn't have ridden it.
I saw you riding.
It looked too scary to ride it.
Did you see us?
- We didn't see you.
- I saw you from over here.
- Did you see us?
- I ran out...
- Did you?
- but you were already gone.
- Unpack first.
- Okay.
I should unpack.
Sun Young, wake up and unpack now.
(Springing up)
(Where is this and who am I?)
(She can't help but crack up.)
Jung Ah.
In my dream,
I was digging for clams.
Unbelievable.
In my dream, I dug up squids too.
I woke up for a second.
Then I fell asleep again and dreamt about digging.
Did you dig up a lot?
There were some earthworms.
I got some that looked like baby octopuses.
"Then I can put this..."
- "in jjamppong." - It's for jjamppong.
That was what I thought.
You were shooting this show in your dream too.
(Fresh off the Sea is all she can think about.)
(While Sun Young is making her way out of the mudflats,)
(the setting sun slowly paints Taean with its glow.)
(What are our neighbors in Sindu-ri...)
(cooking for dinner?)
(Ms. Jeong Sun Ja)
The clams taste richer and tastier these days.
(Chopping various vegetables)
I use zucchinis and carrots.
Manila clams and chives...
taste really good together.
I made bite-sized round pieces.
(After frying it into bite-sized golden pieces,)
Should I call it Manila clam and vegetable jeon?
(healthy and tasty...)
(Manila clam and vegetable jeon are ready.)
(The leftover Manila clams are boiled with chives.)
It's called Manila clam soup. It's healthy.
These are peas I picked outside.
(After placing the rice with the peas she grew...)
(White kimchi, steamed eggs, young napa cabbage kimchi, and more)
(This is the dinner table at Taean...)
(filled with the best of the season.)
(How about their dinner?)
(With lots of Manila clams they harvested themselves,)
(they'll make spicy Manila clam jjamppong.)
(Incredible ingredients)
(Incredible dishes)
(And...)
(What do I do with the chilis after rinsing them?)
(And an incredible performance)
(Screaming)
(Siblings' Chinese Restaurant filled with laughter...)
(is open now.)
Let's only grab what we need today.
(They prepare the ingredients first.)
- The small octopus over here.
- Dark soy sauce.
- Should I take it out now?
- And the noodles and the eggs.
We have to take all the vegetables.
(Manila clams, small octopus, squid, Chinese noodles,)
(bell peppers, onions, pork, cucumber, button mushrooms,)
(soy sauce, sugar, green onions, minced garlic, starch, eggs...)
I'm confused because there are so many.
What do I have to do?
- Okay. Give it to me.
- It's heavy.
No, it's okay.
- It's heavy, indeed.
- It's heavy.
I see. It's okay.
Jjamppong requires so many ingredients.
We're in trouble.
What was this?
What was I going to do?
(So hectic)
I came to grab something, but I can't remember.
(They grabbed all the ingredients, which made Jang Ah hectic.)
What should I do, Jung Ah?
We have to decide the order of the cooking.
We'll finish the smashed cucumber salad first.
- Then we'll make pepper japchae.
- Okay.
Then the meat. We cook tangsuyuk.
(Crushed cucumber salad, pepper japchae, tangsuyuk and jjamppong)
Gosh. I should start this first.
I should quickly make the crushed cucumber salad...
and put it in the fridge.
- Should I rinse them?
- Yes, we have to rinse them all.
(The youngest one in Siblings' Chinese Restaurant's kitchen...)
(volunteers to wash the cucumbers.)
(Washing thoroughly)
The crushed cucumber salad sounds tasty.
(When she was washing them thoroughly...)
(while dreaming of becoming a head chef...)
I'll put the stuff that needs to be washed in here.
(I'll put the stuff that needs to be washed in here.)
Please wash these too.
You just need to rinse these lightly.
We need to rinse the shrimp too.
We also need to rinse the Manila clams.
(Bell peppers, green onions, chili peppers, onions, and more)
(In that case...)
(She pulls her bangs tightly back like always.)
(Should I go for it now?)
Onions.
(Napa cabbages)
(Zucchinis)
(Green onions)
(Julienned bamboo shoots)
(And she never loses her tough pose.)
- Yoon Seo.
- Yes?
Because you're using the water...
It's better with this.
- Is it better?
- Yes.
(Sun Young feels bad for Yoon Seo because there are many to wash.)
(In the end, she rinses them with her.)
- Squid?
- Yes.
I'll place it in the water.
(Sun Young starts to rinse...)
(the seafood for jjamppong.)
Wait, as for the small octopus,
don't we need to purge it with salt?
Does anyone know how to do it?
Well. Salt is...
No. I just wash it with water...
and add to the pot.
- Sun Young.
- Hold on. Let me ask.
Jung Ah, to clean the small octopus,
don't we need to use salt water or flour?
You rub it with flour...
to clean its legs...
and the suction cups.
Flour.
(Will Sun Young, a novice cook, be able to do it?)
(She pours the flour like Jung Ah told her to.)
I've never done this in my life.
(Excited already)
I'm trying it for the first time.
(The small octopus foresaw its fate.)
(Run.)
Look how alive it is.
Look at those suction cups. It's so much alive.
It's escaping.
(She subdues it easily with her bare hands.)
Am I doing it right, Jung Ah?
Jung Ah, do I clean it like this?
It's alive.
(Boldly washing the small octopus)
(Kneading)
I love how it feels.
(She's amazing.)
This is so interesting.
(Sun Young finds cleaning the small octopus the easiest.)
(Next is today's main ingredient, Manila clams.)
These are the Manila clams we dug up today.
(As for the precious Manila clams fresh off the sea,)
(she rinses them more carefully.)
They look so good.
(Manila clams say, "It's refreshing.")
(Clattering)
(While she cleans them with a pleasant sound...)
(Chopping)
(What is this sound?)
(Sun Young prepares the vegetables...)
(at an amazing speed this time.)
You can go slow, Sun Young.
That's something I can't do.
(She chops the vegetables at lightning speed...)
(as she is Wasp Sun Young.)
Gosh. You're good at chopping.
(Amazed)
(Chopping)
(The pleasant chopping sound spreads across the yard.)
Sun Young, you sound like Han Seok Bong's mother.
"You will rinse the clams..."
"while I chop the onions."
("Yes, Mother.")
(While the sisters are busy prepping the ingredients,)
(the brick stoves is almost ready too.)
(After placing the last 2 bricks,)
- It's perfect.
- Okay.
We did a good job.
(the sturdy stoves are ready...)
(to handle the siblings' dishes.)
We don't need to burn the firewood yet, right?
- No.
- Okay.
How can I help?
I'm making the crushed cucumber salad,
so you need to strike them, You Seok.
- Do I strike the cucumbers?
- Yes.
With my fist?
"With my fist?"
Why would you strike the cucumbers with your fist?
(Please spare the cucumbers.)
(What should I strike them with?)
- Now?
- No.
(First, she puts the cucumbers with trimmed ends in a bag.)
You know what the crushed cucumber salad looks like, right?
- I do.
- Okay.
I brought you a mallet.
(He needs to smash them with the mallet, not his fist.)
(You Seok tries smashing cucumbers for the first time.)
Goodness.
(He grabs the mallet.)
(He starts to beat the cucumbers.)
(Crushing)
(Joyful pounding)
(In Search of Taean's Sound)
(This is the sound made by Kang You Seok,)
(who lives in Sindu-ri, Taean-gun, South Chungcheong Province,)
(to make a smashed cucumber salad.)
(After smashing them hard a few more times,)
I smashed them this much.
(they are completely crushed.)
(He pours the well-smashed cucumber into a bowl.)
(It is seasoned with salt and sugar.)
(Jung Ah also adds a generous amount of vinegar to add the tang.)
(Lastly, she gives it a nice mix...)
(after adding minced garlic and sesame seeds.)
(Then sweet and sour smashed cucumber salad is done.)
- Here.
- Do you want to try it?
Will you tell me what I should add more?
I'd love to.
(Sun Young tastes it.)
- It's good.
- It's sweet and salty.
Jung Ah, please give me another piece.
(Putting another piece into her mouth)
- Yes.
- It's tasty.
I can't wait to eat it.
(Its refreshing kick whets her palate.)
(Next, it's time to make pepper japchae.)
(Smashed cucumber salad, pepper japchae, tangsuyuk, jjamppong)
(But they are still prepping the ingredients.)
(At that moment, Jung Seok suddenly goes to the room.)
(He grabs the acoustic guitar he saw earlier.)
(Then he comes back to the yard.)
Sing us a work song.
Yes. Sing us a song.
(A work song? Really?)
(What song will he sing for them?)
(Tuning)
How many chili peppers should I chop lengthwise, Jung Ah?
- How many should I chop?
- Lengthwise
He's singing.
(The performance starts without a warning.)
(Lengthwise, Jung Ah)
(Humming)
I love it.
He's singing.
(He's happy to watch him sing in the 1st row.)
(Singing)
(I want to eat it)
(The pepper japchae)
(Singing random stuff with his sweet voice)
(I want to eat it)
(Based on the lyrics,)
(he must be dying to have some pepper japchae.)
(Still, they get immersed in his song.)
Gosh. Look at him. He's amazing.
(There are his fans everywhere.)
(Thank you)
(For telling me)
- He's really good.
- That I'm amazing
Go away.
(That's it.)
That was crazy.
(His stunning voice captivated the female fans' hearts.)
- Cho Jung Seok.
- Encore.
(Let's change the mood this time.)
(Singing)
That's great.
What did you do with the chilis after washing them?
What did you do with the washed chili peppers?
(Having a culture shock)
What do we do with the chilis after washing them?
Did you drain them?
What do we do?
(There they are)
(Please tell me)
(Singing)
I want to know
(They're over here)
(Both Manila clams and chili peppers are in rock spirit.)
(Falling for Jung Seok)
He's good. It's nice to play the guitar well.
(Singing)
(Highest audience satisfaction rate)
He's amazing.
(He's suddenly embarrassed when he's done singing.)
- Sorry.
- I love the metal.
It's so nice...
to have live music when cooking.
- Are we done prepping?
- Yes, we are.
(Prepping is done. Meat, onions, shiitake and button mushrooms,)
(Cheongyang chili pepper, julienned bamboo shoots)
- I'll start the fire, then.
- Okay.
- Should I do it, Jung Seok?
No. I'm a Warrior of Fire.
Really?
(How to start a fire by the Warrior of Fire)
(Get lots of dried firewood first.)
(Stack them in a crisscross pattern for the air to go through.)
(After stacking the firewood,)
(why don't we get the fire roaring?)
(Skillfully fan the fire to supply it with air.)
(Blazing)
(The fire blazes in no time.)
It's done. It's lit.
Gosh. I was back in my element after a while.
(He's the Warrior of Fire, indeed.)
You're good at starting a fire too, Jung Seok.
- Hold on.
- I just need to...
(But...)
- The flames are really strong.
- They are strong.
(It's way too strong.)
I always do this because I'm the Warrior of Fire.
(I'm so the Warrior of Fire.)
(He's funny.)
Can you turn it down?
(By the way, can you lower the heat?)
Of course, I can. Do you want medium heat?
- Yes. Medium heat, please.
- Medium heat? Okay.
(The Warrior can do anything, including the heat control.)
I'll take some out.
(Subdued)
The heat is lowered.
- This will be good.
- It's great.
- Good. Place the wok.
- Okay.
What are you cooking here?
- She'll stir-fry... Pepper japchae.
- Pepper Japchae.
(Adding a generous amount of oil into the heated pan)
- It's still hot.
- It's okay.
(Amid the intense heat...)
This one? Which one should I give you?
(appears a woman.)
(Adding more oil)
(Pouring the pre-seasoned pork)
(She starts stir-frying it joyfully.)
Is there too much pork? It doesn't cook well.
If you want me...
to increase the heat, I can do that.
Should I turn up the heat? Okay.
(The mysterious woman wants a stronger fire.)
- The heat is good now.
- Okay.
(The hot fire can't stop...)
(this master of the smoky flavors.)
It has to be fully cooked.
(Deity Yum of Chinese Cuisine)
(Chinese cuisine is all about smoky flavors.)
(Stir-frying the meat quickly as if charring it over high heat)
(Not holding back on the spicy chili oil)
(Squeezing)
(After adding the julienned bell pepper,)
(mushrooms, onions, chilis, and bamboo shoots,)
(she stir-fries them mercilessly.)
(Blazing)
(This is how to add the smoky flavor.)
Gosh. Look at the fire.
(After adding the smoky flavor,)
(she adds the chili oil for the 2nd time.)
(A strong spiciness is added to the smoky flavor.)
Will you add a bit more chili oil?
(It's not over yet.)
- A swirl of it?
- Yes.
Drizzle it.
Good.
(Cheongyang chili peppers, chili oil, and smoky flavor)
(Unfathomable spiciness)
- Gosh. It looks so good.
- It looks really good.
(People are drooling.)
(Adding umami with the soy sauce and oyster sauce)
It's the oyster sauce.
(For the finishing touch, she adds the black pepper.)
It's hot. I'll do it.
(You Seok takes over...)
(since it must be hot for Jung Ah to be near the fire.)
(She's proud of him.)
(Doing his best)
Stir-fry them...
- until the vegetables are soft.
- Okay.
(After stir-frying them until the vegetables are soft,)
(he coats it with the smoky flavor.)
(Then spicy pepper japchae is ready.)
Is the pepper japchae finished?
- Jung Seok.
- Yes? You try it first.
No.
(Putting in his mouth)
(How is it, Jung Seok?)
Gosh. It's good.
It's tasty.
(Sun Young tries a bite too.)
(It's really tasty, Jung Ah.)
- It's good, isn't it?
- It's sweet. It's crazy.
(Shocked)
How could you do it?
It's so good, Jung Ah.
(It's totally delicious.)
(Amazed)
- It's better than restaurants.
- Exactly.
- Gosh. Seriously.
- It tastes really good.
- Do you have chopsticks?
- Yes.
(She gives some to the production staff to taste.)
(It's so good.)
What tastes good? Is the crushed cucumber salad good too?
When you taste the pepper japchae,
- it'll blow your mind.
- It's tasty right now.
That's done.
(What is the next dish by Deity Yum of Chinese Cuisine?)
I'll make the sauce first.
The sauce can cool down.
Then I'll hurry and make jjamppong.
(Tangsuyuk sauce, jjamppong)
(What's the remaining stove for?)
You will fry the meat for tangsuyuk.
Fry the meat for tangsuyuk.
(Tangsuyuk?)
I have trauma involving tangsuyuk. I'm in trouble.
(Trauma involving tangsuyuk?)
(On "Three Meals a Day: Doctors" back in 2021,)
(Jung Seok fried the meat to make tangsuyuk.)
(Checking the meat after frying it)
Gosh. They're burnt.
(It's completely burnt.)
(When they measured the oil temperature,)
Is it 294°C?
(it was a whopping 294°C.)
(Is it a smelting furnace? It's a volcano. He'll fry the pot.)
(With 3.33 million views on YouTube,)
(Jung Seok's tangsuyuk was the talk of the town.)
(Laughing)
(The temperature itself makes them laugh.)
That's hilarious.
As soon as I put the meat, it was totally burnt.
(His bitter memory of burnt tangsuyuk)
Are you going to try the meat for tangsuyuk, Jung Seok?
Yes. I'll take the responsibility and fry it well.
(Yes. I'll take the responsibility and fry it well.)
He's awesome.
(Jung Seok steps up with confidence.)
This is for tangsuyuk.
(First, he pours a generous amount of oil.)
Here's a thermometer.
- Here's a thermometer.
- Good. I need it.
- Do we have one?
- Yes.
(Lighting up)
- It'll burn without it.
- Yes.
- It'll be a disaster.
- Here.
(Jung Seok obtained a thermometer.)
I won't fail this time.
(Will he be able to erase his past with the burnt tangsuyuk?)
Sauce? Sauce for what?
- For tangsuyuk.
- The tangsuyuk sauce.
I'm going to watch how she makes the tangsuyuk sauce.
(Jung Ah's special tangsuyuk sauce: 1. Add 300ml of water.)
Here's water.
(2. Add 7 tablespoons of soy sauce.)
(3. Add 16 tablespoons of vinegar.)
(4. Add 6 tablespoons of sugar.)
What is dark soy sauce?
It's used frequently to add color to Chinese dishes.
(Stir-frying carrots, cucumbers, wood ear mushrooms, and others.)
(Pouring the sauce base she just made)
(When it comes to a boil,)
It's boiling, Jung Ah.
(pour the starch slurry slowly, so it won't clump.)
(The more starch slurry she puts,)
- It becomes the sauce you know of.
- Yes.
(the shinier the sauce becomes.)
I see.
- It's my first time seeing it.
- It looks good.
Me too.
I think it's done.
I'll take it off the heat once it boils.
(He hasn't even started frying yet.)
(Measuring the temperature)
(Measuring the temperature again)
(He's measuring the oil temperature forever.)
(Looking for the perfect temperature for frying, 170°C)
(Measuring for the last time)
(He finally grabs the meat in the batter Jung Ah made.)
(He adds the batter first to check the temperature again.)
(Adding the meat now)
(It starts bubbling up as soon as he puts it.)
(Adding it without hesitation)
(How will his tangsuyuk turn out?)
(Be sure to turn the meat pieces from time to time...)
They cook at a different pace.
(so that they will be cooked evenly.)
(The tangsuyuk gets fried with delicious sizzles.)
- Once the oil is preheated...
- You must like fried food.
to 170°C, you must fry it immediately.
What's the temperature now?
It's 170°C.
Is it 170°C?
(He measures it once again.)
The temperature is going down.
(Rushing)
I need to bring more firewood.
(He tries to adjust the temperature to 170°C again.)
(Thanks to Jung Seok's effort the tangsuyuk is frying...)
(to a beautiful golden brown at 170°C.)
(Finally, it's time to check.)
(Everyone's attention is on the tangsuyuk.)
(The perfectly golden tangsuyuk)
(Perfectly golden and mouthwatering tangsuyuk)
(A flawless golden color from every angle)
It looks really good.
- Right?
- It turned out very well.
(Golden tangsuyuk born at 170°C)
You look like a professional.
(A mesmerizing sight you can't look away from)
(Going in)
That startled me.
It really startled me.
(The camera rushes over to see the good news.)
(Filming up close)
That's incredible. You're practically a robot.
(We enjoyed looking at it.)
Do you want to taste it?
(The appearance gets a perfect score. How does it taste?)
(Impressed)
- It's insane.
- It's very good.
(A taste that makes you gasp in admiration)
What's the matter with me?
Why am I like this?
(Feeling proud of himself)
How do I take this out?
(Right on cue, the tangsuyuk sauce is ready.)
- Do you want to taste it?
- Sure.
(A tasting?)
I can't just taste it like this.
I have no choice but to dip this in.
(Hunting down a piece of tangsuyuk to taste the sauce)
I have to taste the sauce.
The sauce?
- Is there something wrong?
- No.
(What is he saying?)
Sun Young, there's a small piece.
- I didn't see it.
- Really?
I was too busy...
(The bigger the bite, the better the taste)
It's the best tangsuyuk I ever had.
- Really?
- Yes.
Didn't Jung Seok say that he was a terrible cook?
You're good at cooking.
- Cooking?
- Yes.
(A special compliment)
It looks really good.
I can't wait to eat it.
(The legendary tangsuyuk that leaves everyone in awe)
You mastered the art of frying.
You just have to get the right temperature.
- At 170°C?
- Yes, at 170°C.
(I am...)
(Speaking in Chinese)
(a master of tangsuyuk.)
Viewers, are you watching?
(You can...)
(also make good tangsuyuk.)
It's very good. My tangsuyuk is a big success.
Please forget about disaster in the past.
(Please forget about the burnt tangsuyuk)
(The Siblings' Chinese Restaurant's one last shot)
(Manila clam jjamppong)
(After the first bite,)
(the praise comes flying.)
(Completely lost in it)
(Even the chef is very satisfied.)
(Siblings' Chinese Restaurant is open for rave reviews.)
(I’m curious about where we’re working tomorrow.)
(Just tell us whether it’s on land or somewhere else.)
(I said I'd only love garlic.)
(This time, it's garlic, the comfort food for Koreans.)
(A financial crisis hits the siblings?)
(We're doomed.)
(Who says that we're doomed?)
(15, 16...)
(You're with the savvy art major.)
(We'll work hard too.)
(A round of applause to compliment)
(We made it through another day.)
(In the meantime, a bromance blossoms.)
(What do you girls do when I leave?)
(We're going to have fun from now on.)
(Getting ready for an outing)
("I'll set you free." The beloved art major)
("The secret was in the bread." Miss Yum's ageless beauty)
(A youthful star appears, You James Dean)
(California Auntie, Jennica Kim)
(Back to the 60s and 90s, it's coming soon.)